PROVINSI DKI JAKARTA JAKARTA TIMUR

NIK

T .

: 3175050601930004

Nama KUSENO HADI PRABOWO JAKARTA, 06-01-1993 Jenis kelamin JAKARTA, 06-01-



# KARTU KELUARGA

No.3175050501096851

Nama Kepala Keluarga Alamat

RT/RW

REPUBLIK INDONESIA Kode Pos

KUSNO

JL SRIKAYA NO.54 012/009 : 13770

Desa/Kalurahan Kecamatan

CIJANTUNG PASAR REBO

Kabupaten/Kota Provinsi

: JAKARTA TIMUR : DKI JAKARTA

No	Nama Lengkap	NIK	Jenis Kelamin	Tempat Lahir	Tanggal Lahir	Agama	Pendidikan	Jenis Pekerjaan	Golengan Darah
		(8)	(3)		(9)	(8)	7)	(a)	(2)
1	KUSNO	3175051012520004	LAIG-LAIG	AKARTA	10-12-1902	ISLAM	SLTPISEDERAJAT	MRASWASTA	0
2	PARTININGSIH	3175054108620002	PEREMPUAN	PEKALONGAN	01-09-1962	ISLAM	SLTP/SEDERAJAT	MENGURUS RUMAH TANGGA	0
3	KHALIYAH PERTIWI	3175054703840006	PEREMPLIAN	JANARTA	07-03-1934	ISLAM	AKADEMI/DIPLOMA NISARJANA MUDA	KARYAWAN SWASTA	0
4	KUSENO HADI PRABOWO	3175050601930004	LAKELAN	JAKARTA	06-01-1993	ISLAM	SLTASEDERAJAT	PELAJAR/MAHASISWA	ð
5	MUHAMMAD MAULANA KUSPARTOMO	3175050904060001	LAKI-LAN	JAKARTA	03-04-2006	ISLAM	SLTP/SEDERAJAT	PELAJAR/MAHASISWA	9
5	•			8			•		*
7	w			=			-		a
8	*			*			-	*	
9	2			a	-		-	-	2
10	*			c					-

No.	Status Perkawinan	Tanggal Perkawinan	Status Hubungan Dalam Keluarga	Kewarganegaraan	Dokumen Imigrasi		Nama Orang Tua		
					No. Paspor	No. KITAP	Ayah	lbu	
	(10)	(11)	(12)	(13)	(14)	(15)	(16)	11 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1	
1	KAWIN TERCATAT	19-03-1983	KEPALA KELUARGA	WNI	5	2	MOHAMAD MUKSIN	HALITAN	
2	KAWINTERCATAT	19-03-1983	ISTERI	WHI	•		DALARI	MLIKARAMAH	
3	BELUM KAWIN	*	ANAK	WNI		3	KUSNO	PARTININGSIH	
4	BELUM KAWIN	۰	ANAK	WNI	2		KUSNO	PARTININGSIH	
5	BELUM KAWIN		ANAK	WNI	4	8	KUSNO	PARTININGSIH	
6	•	-	•			a:			
7			•		3	5	-	4.	
8	•	-	•				-		
9			4	A		a			
10	*	-	•				1-		

Dikeluarkan Tanggal :

05-04-2021

KEPALA KELUARGA

A.N.KA.SUDIN DUKCAPIL JAKARTA TIMUR KA. SEKTOR



M. HOTIB, SH. MH NIP. 196309291985031011

KUSNO Tanda Tangan/Cap Jempol



# **KUSENO HADI PRABOWO**

Jl. Srikaya No. 54 E RT 12 RW 09 Cijantung, Jakarta Timur HP: 085921317725 Email: kusenohadi@gmail.com

"I am competent in construction, hard worker and willing to learn new things.

I am able to work well both individually and as part of team

I am sure that my work experiences will contribute positively for the team i work with.

I am ready to be located on the mining site"

## Personal Information

Marital status: Single

Nationality : Indonesian

Date of birth: January 6th, 1993

Gender : Male Religion : Moslem

### Education

Bachelor's Degree (S1) Civil Engineering, University of Bung Karno, 2018

Senior High School, SMK Negeri 52, Jakarta

Junior High School, SLTP Negeri 179, Jakarta

Elementary School, SDN Cijantung 07, Jakarta

# Qualification

#### **Computer Literate:**

Ms. Word, Excel, Power Point, & Internet.

Computer Skill: AutoCad 2010

## Work Experiences

January 2018 - present

PT ANGGIRA CIPTA UTAMA

**Line of Business:** 

**Construction Maintenance** 

Position:

Asst. Supervisor

#### Responsibilities:

- Supervise the project
- Calculate the work volume
- Purchase project material

December 2016 - December 2017

PT. SINERGI VISI NUSANTARA

**Line of Business:** 

**Construction Maintenance** 

**Position:** 

Administration Project and Purchasing

April 2012 - November 2016

PT DATATEL INDONESIA

**Line of Business:** 

Construction of Telecommunication

**Position:** 

Administration Project

#### Responsibilities:

- Preparing invoices for clients.
- Drawing layout by AutoCAD
- Coordinate jobs on filed

# Trainings

#### Pelatihan Mandiri Jarak Jauh Bidang Konstruksi

Setara 56 jam Pelajaran (JPL).

Pada Jabatan : Ahli Muda K-3 Konstruksi

Direktorat Jenderal Bina Konstruksi - Kementerian Pekerjaan Umum dan Perumahan Rakyat

### Pelatihan Mandiri Jarak Jauh Bidang Konstruksi

Setara 56 jam Pelajaran (JPL).

Pada Jabatan: Manajer Lapangan Pelaksanaan Konstruksi Bangunan Gedung

Direktorat Jenderal Bina Konstruksi - Kementerian Pekerjaan Umum dan Perumahan Rakyat